Contact

713-392-5386 (Mobile) merryrivers@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mary-m-rios-bsn-cmsrn-cen-aa743622 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Healthcare

Patient Safety

Certifications

BLS

ACLS

PALS

Certified Medical Surgical Nurse TNCC

Mary M. Rios BSN, CMSRN, CFN

Interim Director of Nursing at Rehoboth McKinley Christian Health Care Services

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Patient Care Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Consulting, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Nursing Documentation, and Workplace Safety. Strong professional with a Masters focused in Healthcare Administration/Clinical Informatics from University of Phoenix.

Experience

Rehoboth McKinley Christian Health Care Services Interim Director of Nursing January 2020 - Present (5 months) Gallup, NM, United States

Aurora St. Luke's Medical Center 1 year 11 months

Interim Director of Nursing May 2018 - August 2018 (4 months)

Milwaukee, Wisconsin

Medical Telemetry Units

Interim-Patient Care Manager: Neuro-Surgical, Medical-Tele, Ortho-Spine Surgical Units

October 2016 - May 2018 (1 year 8 months)

Milwaukee, Wisconsin

Cordova Community Medical Ctr Interim CNO March 2016 - September 2016 (7 months) Cordova, Alaska

Aurora Health Care

Interim Patient Care Manager: Med-Surg, ICU & ACE Unit November 2015 - January 2016 (3 months)

Cudahy, Wisconsin

Maior Logistics
Director of Nursing Services-Part-Time
July 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Bay Area Medical Center Interim Director- Medical-Surgical Service Line January 2015 - May 2015 (5 months) Marinette, Wisconsin

Cleveland Clinic Abu Dhabi Healthcare Clinical Subject Matter Expert (SME) Consultant September 2011 - July 2012 (11 months) Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

Methodist Healthcare System Nursing Director February 2009 - July 2011 (2 years 6 months) San Antonio, Texas Area

The Methodist Hospital System
Director of Nursing
March 1995 - July 2008 (13 years 5 months)

Education

University of Phoenix

Masters, Healthcare Administration/Clinical Informatics · (2016 - 2019)

University of Phoenix
Bachelors of Science, Nursing (2006 - 2008)

Houston Community College Associates Degree, Nursing · (1992 - 1995)